# INOK **LIM**

778-996-9209 inoklim@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/inoklim inok-lim.github.io ⊕



### **OBJECTIVE**

Bright, talented, agile and self-motivated web developer with a background in visual design and educational technology. Prototyped and developed more than 10 new product features for the last eight years for Sage Software Canada Ltd., a leading accounting and ERP software development company. Consistently received high user experience scores for all new feature and UI modernization projects. Passionate about building creative and accessible web applications.



### **SKILLS**

- UI /UXDesign Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Figma, AdobeXD, Axure RP
- Motion Design Adobe Animation, After Effect, Flash
- Web development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.JS, Jekyll, GitHub, MySQL
- Content Management System / e-Learning WordPress, Drupal



#### EXPERIENCE

# **Web Developer and UI/UX Designer | Sage Software Canada Ltd.**, Richmond, BC MARCH 2015 – PRESENT

- Developed front-end for Sage300 Cloud's user experience using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Designed wire-frames, prototypes and user interfaces for more than 10 new projects and feature products each year
- Ensured visual and UX design consistency across the product
- Improved Web content accessibility and usability by 83% compliance to WCAG and WAI-ARIA accessibility standards
- Managed best practice HTML/CSS and streamlined CSS styling process with LESS/SASS to reduce production time

# **Digital Media Designer | Best Buy Canada**, Burnaby, BC AUGUST 2014 – JANUARY 2015

- Designed weekly e-Newsletters in bi-lingual in timely manner
- Developed interactive motion graphic banners for web and mobile devices
- Produced marketing signage, brochures and flyers

## **Web Designer and Multimedia Developer | Member 365**, Ottawa, ON AUGUST 2005 – JUNE 2013

- Designed websites for desktop and mobile
- Converted mockups into HTML templates
- Developed e-learning and interactive multimedia projects using WordPress, Drupal, Flash and JavaScript for clients including Starbucks, Burger King, Health Canada, Canadian War Museum, NRC

## **Graphic Designer | Skyblace Communications Inc.**, Ottawa, ON JANUARY 2004 – JULY 2005

- Designed logos, brand promotion materials
- Developed event web sites and multimedia kits

## Interactive Multimedia Designer | SIGPRO Wireless Inc., Ottawa, ON SEPTEMBER 2001 – DECEMBER 2003

- Designed marketing and sale promotion materials
- Designed and developed Computer Based Training tools using WordPress, DreamWeaver, Flash and JavaScript
- Designed product sketches and 3D graphics for engineers using Illustrator and CAD
- Supported organizing trade shows and conferences
- Won Ward of Appreciation in April 2002 and Award of Excellence for the hard work and contribution to the company in November 2002



#### **EDUCATION**

Interactive Multimedia Design | Post Diploma | Algonquin College, Ottawa JANUARY 2000 – SEPTEMBER 2001

**Computer Graphics | Certificate | Jung Ang Computer Academy**, Seoul JANUARY 1998 – DECEMBER 1998

**Educational Technology | Bachelor's Degree | Hanyang University,** Seoul MARCH 1993 – FEBRUARY 1997